

Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9ki/



Graduated in Management Processes, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I have always had the desire to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally, I got in touch with the technology area about 10 years ago and since the end of 2019, I have returned to the technology area. where I've been studying and taking different courses. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I have learned many new things and evolved day by day.

I will continue to improve myself daily as a Front-end Developer and Software Engineer after graduation, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



EXPERIENCE

Full Technical Consultant

January 2022 - April 2022

DT3 Sports

Invoice issuance, marketplaces, content creation for campaigns, website development in React.JS, image optimization and responsible for the integration of ERP Bling.

VILT Brazil Information Systems

Adobe Experience Manager(AEM),

using Platform programs

providing services for

Fullstack Consulting, working with Java

in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend,

several clients such as Porto, CVC and etc.

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

February 2019 - June 2021

Nova Lik Auto Peças

Issuance of Sales Invoice
Issuance of Payment Reports
Input and Output of Products in Stock.

Office Assistant

November 2014 - June 2018

M

Quality and Service Technician

June 2010 - July 2013

Arcos Dourados LTDA.

Make employees work coordinated in their respective functions, for better customer service and delivery of a 100% qualitative product.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Faculdade Única

2021 - 2022

MBA Software Engineering

Estácio de Sá - RJ

2018 - 2020

TECHNOLOGIST Management processes



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



HTML/CSS - 3 Years of Experience

Jquery/Javascript - 3 Years of Experience

Angular/React - 3 Years of Experience

VueJs/NodeJs - 3 Years of Experience

Git/Github - 3 Years of Experience

NPM/YARN - 3 Years of Experience

Wordpress/Shopify/Bling - 3 Years of Experience

Bootstrap/Typescript - 2 Years of Experience

UI/UX - 2 Years of Experience

Figma/Photoshop - 2 Years of Experience

Less/Sass - 1 Year of Experience

GitLab/Sketch - 3 Months of Experience

AWS/PHP - 1 month of Experience

Firebase/Laravel - 1 month of Experience

Markdown/Evernote - 1 month of Experience

Strapi/GraphQL - 1 month of Experience

MongoDB/MariaDB - 1 month of Experience

MySQL/NoSQL - 1 month of Experience

PostgreSQL/Express - 1 month of Experience

Babel/Webpack - 1 month of Experience

Postman/NextJS - 1 month of Experience

Jest/JUnit - 1 month of Experience

Mongoose/Nginx - 1 month of Experience

TailwindCSS - 1 month of Experience



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - Digital Innovation - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Front-End Developer - 2022

Working with Components in React - 2022

Component architecture and front-end complexity management - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS - FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ – Udemy – 2020

Digital Security Course - FGV - 2020

Business Financial Education Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Strategic Planning Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Management Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Customer Success Course (How to Conquer and Keep Customers)

– SEBRAE –
2020

Digital Marketing Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Strategy for Growth Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Basic Platform Security Course (CBSP) - Shelter Courses, 2018

Submerged Aircraft Escape Training (HUET) – Shelter Courses, 2018

Administrative Assistant Course - 24-hour Courses - 2016



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ _hudson.9kj/



Spanish - Basic

French - Basic

Italian - Basic

English - Advanced



ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel

Word

Power Point

Teams

Outlook

Sketch

Wordpress

Shopify

ERP Bling

System Configurations

Windows

Computer Domain

Typing

document archiving

internet in general

Google Chrome

Mozilla

Opera